<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Capital Technology Services</title>
    <description>Capital Technology Services specializes in web application development in Ruby and PHP. The company has development staff based in Philadelphia, PA and Nashville, TN.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:15:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rails Asset Pipeline Issue in Google App Engine Flexible Environment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We attempted a deployment of a Ruby on Rails application to Google App Engine’s environment yesterday (2017-01-12) and the links to all of our assets broke. In short, roll back the version of Google’s Cloud Components and it will probably fix your links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-problem---no-fingerprints-on-assets&quot;&gt;The Problem - No Fingerprints on Assets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of most deployments we will run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gcloud components update&lt;/code&gt; when
Google prompts that there’s a new release of their Cloud SDK. Who doesn’t? We
all want to make sure we have access to the cool new feature’s in Google’s Cloud
SDK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We deployed a client application after beginning of the new year, a week went
by and we were ready for the next deployment. We pushed a new version up and
all of the links to Javascript, CSS, and images were broken. After combing
through the source code changes and looking for a commit that broke our asset
pipeline configuration, we turned up nothing. Our links still looked like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;/stylesheets/application.css
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;instead of this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;/stylesheets/application-cb6e77b89d7e2f628faf475f1ff924935e65036aec2a332d16f228aa687f23c7.css
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-solution---restore-cloud-sdk-components&quot;&gt;The Solution - Restore Cloud SDK Components&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we confirmed there was nothing wrong with our application’s configuration
we decided to roll back absolutely everything to be in line with our last
deployment, which meant running:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;gcloud components restore
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This restored us to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Google Cloud SDK 135.0.0
bq 2.0.24
bq-nix 2.0.24
core 2016.11.11
core-nix 2016.11.07
gcloud 
gsutil 4.22
gsutil-nix 4.18
kubectl 
kubectl-darwin-x86_64 1.4.4
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After running another deployment we confirmed that all of our assets and their
fingerprints were back and we could move forward. We don’t know the exact cause
for the problem yet. As of this morning the latest available Google Cloud SDK is
139.0.0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Google Cloud SDK 139.0.0
bq 2.0.24
bq-nix 2.0.24
core 2017.01.11
core-nix 2016.11.07
gcloud 
gsutil 4.22
gsutil-nix 4.18
kubectl 
kubectl-darwin-x86_64 1.5.1
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-note-on-deployment&quot;&gt;A Note on Deployment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A moment to emphasize something important that you should take into account when
deploying to GAE. Don’t just deploy with the default options to automatically
promote the new version and stop the previous version. Do this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;gcloud app deploy --no-promote --no-stop-previous-version
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After your application has been deployed, take the opportunity to confirm that
the new deployment is functional. Then you can use Google’s web based console
to migrate traffic over to the new release when you know everything is working.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/12/rails-in-google-flex-environment-asset-issue.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/12/rails-in-google-flex-environment-asset-issue.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 Resolutions - 3. Adopt Two-Factor Authentication</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;two-factor authentication, authenticating via something you know and something you have (or are), is a crucial strategy for securing your accounts, applications, and ultimately your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;was-a-landmark-year-in-cybersecurity&quot;&gt;2016 was a landmark year in cybersecurity…&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…for all the wrong reasons. The fallout related to poor information security
habits is still in the national news even after the end of the election cycle.
But don’t make the mistake of thinking that you couldn’t possibly become the
target of online criminal activity. You don’t have to be a high-profile
politician, celebrity, or even do anything particularly remarkable to have
your personal information stolen. That’s because criminal activity can now be
perpetrated on the scale and with the same ease as you reach thousands of
followers on social media networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why you should take the time right now to proactively put your account
security back in your hands, and adopt two-factor authentication (2FA).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;youve-already-used-two-factor-authentication&quot;&gt;You’ve already used two-factor authentication&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever you go to an ATM, you have to provide your PIN after inserting a card
into the machine. The card is something your have. The PIN is something that you
know. Using an ATM involves a form of two-factor authentication. It’s not hard,
and you know that it provides a measure of safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, in order to get into your e-mail, file servers, and
applications with critical business information you’re probably only using
something you know, a password. Some of you are using the same password for
multiple accounts. Even worse, some of you have an Excel document on your
system where you store all of the passwords and PIN information that cannot
share the same common password you like to use everywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-risks-are-all-around-you&quot;&gt;The risks are all around you&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last year, we have seen plenty of bad passwords, stored insecurely, and
shared indiscriminately. What you don’t see are the poor storage of credentials
on behalf of the website you just signed up for, the lack of encryption on your
company’s blog, and the malware that is feeding information from your
accountant’s computer to someone neither you nor your accountant knows is
looking at your data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adopting two-factor authentication doesn’t mitigate all of these risks. But it’s
a step in the right direction. Inputting a six-digit code when you access a
critical account takes a few extra seconds and means that someone a world away
is less likely to be able to login to the account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-supports-2fa&quot;&gt;Who supports 2FA?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twofactorauth.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twofactorauth.org&lt;/a&gt;
they have a fairly extensive list of businesses whose technology offerings
support two-factor authentication. They also help you notify institutions that
you’re looking for them to adopt 2FA by providing links to Twitter and Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your favorite bank, e-commerce site, or local government isn’t on the list
still make sure to dig through your account settings and look for 2FA account
configuration options. Sometimes the option is present but not easy to find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;opt-for-hardware-tokens-and-apps-instead-of-sms&quot;&gt;Opt for hardware tokens and apps instead of SMS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recently released documents from the National Institute of Standards and
Technology (NIST) they’ve made clear that SMS and voice call based 2FA are
possibly subject to interception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Due to the risk that SMS messages or voice calls may be intercepted or
redirected, implementers of new systems SHOULD carefully consider
alternative authenticators. If the out-of-band verification is to be made
using the public switched telephone network (PSTN), the verifier SHALL
verify that the pre-registered telephone number being used is not associated
with a VoIP (or other software-based) service. It then sends the SMS or
voice message to the pre-registered telephone number. Changing the
pre-registered telephone number SHALL NOT be possible without two-factor
authentication at the time of the change.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of using SMS, if your provider allows you to use a program like
Google Authenticator or Authy, use those programs instead. If you’re really
zealous about keeping your authentication codes secret, here are links to the
RFC documents describing &lt;a href=&quot;https://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6238&quot;&gt;TOTP&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&quot;https://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc4226&quot;&gt;HOTP&lt;/a&gt; algorithms:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wait-what-about-my-companys-software&quot;&gt;Wait, what about my company’s software!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, if you’re a company with a custom web application we can help you and
your clients to further secure account authentication by adding in 2FA. It’s
easier than you think and can be applied selectively so that users who are
concerned with security can adopt 2FA at their own pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sales@cts-llc.net?subject=I need two-factor authentication&quot;&gt;Contact us to about enabling two-factor authentication in your software.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/03/adopt-2fa.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/03/adopt-2fa.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 Resolutions - 2. Measure Site Performance</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If your site is slow to load you’re losing mobile market share and better placement in search engine results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;you-know-the-frustration&quot;&gt;You know the frustration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve been there, trying to load your website during a presentation or sharing
a link with a lead while at their location, and the page… just… won’t…
finish… loading. Maybe you tell the audience to try loading the site at work.
Maybe it’s your mobile phone provider’s problem, they’re always slow in this
part of town. Maybe your computer is getting old and you need a new one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;or-maybe-your-sites-hosting-isnt-configured-properly&quot;&gt;Or maybe your site’s hosting isn’t configured properly&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your front page assets total several megabytes in uncompressed images
with an unnecessarily large color palette&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The JavaScript, CSS, and markup for the site isn’t compressed and “minified”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There are no cache control directives on your site, so browsers request
assets that they don’t need to update&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your web server responds, “slowly”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How on earth would you ever know any of the above? By consulting the following
tools right now:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.google.com/speed/pagespeed/insights/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Google PageSpeed Insights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://tools.pingdom.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pingdom Website Speed Test&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eek-i-got-a-50100&quot;&gt;Eek! I got a 50/100!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t surprising, but it probably isn’t hard to fix either. The most common
error that we see is that the dimensions of images are considerably larger than
they need to be. On one company’s staff page, the images were sixteen times the
size that they would ever be rendered for a desktop browser. Complaints about
compression, minification, and cache control headers usually require a quick
tweak to your web server’s configuration files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-got-a-75100-and-i-have-never-been-a-c-student&quot;&gt;I got a 75/100 and I have never been a “C” student!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relax a bit. These tests are very tough to get a perfect score on and were
engineered as a measuring stick for sites with hundreds of thousands of daily
visitors. Just because you got an “average” grade doesn’t mean that you’re
doing poorly. But what you probably should do is check the PageSpeed Insight
scores of your competitors. Search engines take into account how quickly a site
loads as well as the relevance of the content. So with all other things being
equal, you want to make sure you’re at least a little faster than your
competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;think-about-mobile-clients&quot;&gt;Think about mobile clients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In your home and office, you probably have a broadband connection. The Google
Pagespeed Insights and Pingdom tests are located in data centers with even
better connectivity than your home or office. Now consider that mobile bandwidth
varies based on multiple factors such as wireless network coverage, network
congestion, and physical obstacles to radio signals. If your business is
reliant on customers accessing your sites with mobile devices, you’re going to
need to be extra vigilant about performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;set-a-standard&quot;&gt;Set a standard&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim for initial page load times of under 1.5 seconds in all of the Rails
applications that we build. That can be an ambitious target on media rich
websites, but there are strategies for achieving fast load times beyond basic
server configuration tweaks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sales@cts-llc.net?subject=Improve My Site Performance&quot;&gt;Contact us to improve your website’s performance.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/02/check-your-pagespeed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/02/check-your-pagespeed.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 Resolutions - 1. Improve Your SSL Configuration</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When users connect to your website are you sure that the data they send you is properly secured?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ask-yourself-the-following-questions&quot;&gt;Ask yourself the following questions:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do users (i.e. my customers, my staff, or myself) log into my website?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do users buy anything on my website?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do users share information with my business via forms hosted on my website?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continue reading if the answer to any of these questions was, “yes”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;would-you-be-concerned-if&quot;&gt;Would you be concerned if?:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The contents of the forms submitted on your site were shared with others&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The credit card information of your customers was visible to others&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The username and passwords of your users were vulnerable to interception&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re concerned, and you should be, take a minute to test your site’s SSL
configuration. Qualys
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/qualys&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;(@qualys)&lt;/a&gt;
has been providing an excellent tool for years available at
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssllabs.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.ssllabs.com&lt;/a&gt;.
When you arrive click on “Test your server”, and enter your site’s hostname
(i.e. www.yourdomainname.com) in the form. If you receive less than an, “A”
letter grade, contact us. If your site is running on the Apache or NGINX we
servers, we have a configuration that will improve your score and protect the
communication between your website and users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;if-you-get-an-a-or-an-a&quot;&gt;If you get an “A” or an “A+”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, you’re better off than the majority of websites on the
Internet. However, just because you have a proper SSL installation doesn’t mean
that it’s being used properly. We still see plenty of websites that have good
SSL configurations that fail to enforce the use of HTTPS when logging in,
submitting forms, and completing purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sales@cts-llc.net?subject=Improve My SSL Configuration&quot;&gt;Contact us to test and improve your SSL installation.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/01/new-years-resolutions-better-ssl-security.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/01/new-years-resolutions-better-ssl-security.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Website Audit Checklist</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Checklist for setting up WordPress from scratch on a Debian or Ubuntu virtual machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Traffic&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Approximately how many visitors per week/month does the site receive?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Where are those visitors located?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Where do those visitors come to the site from?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Technical&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Where is the web site hosted?&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Who is in control of the hosting account?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What software is serving up the web site? (e.g. WordPress)&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Who has access to the software?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;What functionality is provided by the software?&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;If the site is WordPress based, we want to know every plugin that is
currently installed so that we can account for caring for or replacing
that plugin.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Where are the DNS records hosted?&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Who has control of the DNS records?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Where is the e-mail service associated with the domain hosted?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Which analytics/tracking vendors connected to the site?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Are there any feeds or APIs provided by the current site that will be
disruptive if replaced?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What are the most popular browsers desktop/tablet/mobile that compose
greater than 90% of marketshare regionally/nationally/globally at the time
of this audit?&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;For example: Google Chrome is currently 63.19% of the desktop world
marketshare, Firefox is 14.59%, Internet Explorer is 9.73%, Safari is
5.29%, and Microsoft Edge is 3.06%. Together they make of 95.86% of the
desktop markestshare. If the site is targeting a global audience of mostly
desktop users, these browsers should be frequently tested for
compatibility.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;If the client is in a corporate environment where Microsoft Edge or
Internet Explorer make up a larger share of likely users, it would merit
greater attention being paid to that platform.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Languages&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Is the site being offered in more than one language?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Which languages is the site being offered in?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Is content manually or machine translated?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Security&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Is HTTPS enforced on every connection?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Is HTTPS enforced on login?&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;The&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;What is the Qualys letter grade for the SSL/TLS installation?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Performance&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;What is the Google PageSpeed Insights score for the site on mobile and
desktop?&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;45/100 and 50/100&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Which suggestions does GPSI make for improving the performance of the
site?&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Optimize Images&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Eliminate render-blocking JavaScript and CSS in above-the-fold content&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Leverage browser caching&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Minify CSS&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Minify JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Compressing and selecting appropriately sized images is going to be an
ongoing battle. It’s our experience that after a perfectly tuned site
is delivered to a customer, that the next front page article is
published with an image with dimensions well above the necessary
dimensions, and color depth beyond what is perceptible. This leads to
an extremely slow loading site.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Browser caching headers are quite an easy fix at the web server level.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;p&gt;Minification of CSS and JavaScript can also be handled at the software
or web server level with minimal effort.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;What usability suggestions does GPSI make on mobile?&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Size tap targets appropriately&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Size content to viewport&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/11/26/website-audit-checklist.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/11/26/website-audit-checklist.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Billing Checklist</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This checklist guides operations staff to make sure that invoicing and payments to contractors are executed thoroughly and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If it is the 1st or the 16th of the month, developers are instructed to send
in time records to their project management contact. Gather these records on
a per project basis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Process the timesheets which involves extracting date, duration, and
comments for inclusion on the bottom notes of the invoice. Take the sum of
the hours and create line items for each at the top of the invoice.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Evaluate the hosting expenses associated with each client and add them to
the invoice, creating a recurring invoice when necessary.
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Amazon Web Services&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Heroku&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Rackspace&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Google Cloud Services&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;LocaleApp&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/09/07/billing-checklist.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/09/07/billing-checklist.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rails - Converting from Heroku PostgreSQL to Google Cloud SQL (MySQL)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This article covers converting from Heroku PostgreSQL to Google Cloud SQL, which uses MySQL for its RDBMS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time we deploy clients to Heroku, a very slick and easy to use
Platform as a Service (PaaS). But occasionally we run into clients with a
preference for Google Cloud Services. In this specific case, we started with
the client’s app deployed on Heroku and Heroku’s hosted PostgreSQL database
service. We focused first on deploying the Rails application over to GCS
because there was minimal performance impact to running the database on Heroku’s
PostgreSQL service while the app was hosted on Google. But now we’re back and
we are going to finish the job with a full conversion over to Google’s Cloud SQL
product. That means switching to MySQL. Here’s how to do it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Follow Heroku’s instructions for how to backup and then export the latest
dump of your database to your local machine. At the end of the process you
will have a file named “latest.dump” that you will have downloaded using
curl.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://devcenter.heroku.com/articles/heroku-postgres-import-export&quot;&gt;https://devcenter.heroku.com/articles/heroku-postgres-import-export&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;We have to process this file a bit in order to import it into MySQL and
oddly that means having a local instance of PostgreSQL handy to import and
re-export the data.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use psql to create a transition_database on the local PostgreSQL server.
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;CREATE DATABASE transition_database;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Load the data into a local copy of PostgreSQL:
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pg_restore --verbose --clean --no-acl --no-owner -d transition_database latest.dump&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Export the data again as a collection of INSERT queries instead of COPY,
which is not a statement in the SQL standard.
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pg_dump --data-only --column-inserts --file=import.sql transition_database&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remove all of the SET statements at the top of the import.sql file&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;USE name_of_target_database;&lt;/code&gt; to the top of the import.sql file.
This may not be as important if you’re using the command line client and
specifying the target database on connection. But MySQLWorkbench complained
about not knowing which database to run queries against when I was connected
to the server.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Replace all of the sequence setting statements with alterations of the
autoincrement values on the table. Note that you have to set the
autoincrement value to the value of the PostgreSQL sequence + 1.
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SELECT pg_catalog.setval('addresses_id_seq', 22, true);&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ALTER TABLE addresses AUTO_INCREMENT=23;&lt;/code&gt;
This is tedious if you have a large collection of tables, but can be made
easier by using a regular expression to hunt out and replace lines beginning
with &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;^SELECT&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add the “mysql2” gem to your Gemfile.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle install&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Open your config/database.yml file and add the details of the new MySQL
connection under your production configuration.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rake db:migrate RAILS_ENV=production&lt;/code&gt; This is going to setup your
all of the tables necessary, but they will of course be empty.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IF your import is small:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I used MySQLWorkbench to connect to the Google Cloud SQL instance and
run import.sql.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You could just as easily use the command line client to import the data.
&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;mysql -h IP.ADD.OF.SQL -u USERNAME -p database_name &amp;lt; import.sql&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IF your import is large:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Upload your import.sql file to a Cloud Storage Container&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Go to your database in Google Cloud SQL and import the file by finding
it in the cloud storage container.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/08/26/converting-from-heroku-postgresql-to-google-cloud-sql.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/08/26/converting-from-heroku-postgresql-to-google-cloud-sql.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project Documentation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This article describes the types of documentation that need to accompany each project we’re involved with and standards to which that documentation must conform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are four types of documentation that we need to be concerned with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;User Manual - a manual for the broader user base of the application.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Administration Manual - a manual for project owners on how to care for the
product. This includes documentation for devops and system administrators
that will be caring for the supporting infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;API / Developer Manual - This manual will be produced when the product
features the ability for third party developers to integrate our product
into their products. This is produced in addition to documentation
written in the source code of the product.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Source Documentation - Documentation integrated into the source code of
the product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;user-manual-standards&quot;&gt;User Manual Standards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The user manual is most likely just a subset of the documentation that you would
give to the administrators of the system we’re building. For all of the concepts
in the system that have actions performed upon them you will want a descriptive
paragraph on how to perfom the action and a describe the consequences of that
action. Most applications will have the ability to create, read, update, and
destroy (CRUD) records. Additionally, there’s usually going to be a view for a
list of all of the records of a particular type. All of these things seem self
explanatory to most developers. However, the only way to be certain that users
understand how to take advantage of a system is to document it clearly and
concisely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using the following Markdown template as an example, you can describe any
requirements before engaging in a process, the steps to complete a process, and
any notes relevant to the user upon process completion. For instance, one might
define &lt;strong&gt;requirements&lt;/strong&gt; that in order to create a checking account record one
must know their routing and account number before they begin. After completing
the process steps to add the checking account, one might describe that the
checking account will now be available for use to pay invoices elsewhere in the
system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
  &lt;code&gt;
# Subject

## Index

### Requirements

*
*

### Steps

1.
1.

### Notes

*
*

## Create

### Requirements

*
*

### Steps

1.
1.

### Notes

*
*

## Read

### Requirements

*
*

### Steps

1.
1.

### Notes

*
*

## Update

### Requirements

*
*

### Steps

1.
1.

### Notes

*
*

## Destroy

### Requirements

*
*

### Steps

1.
1.

### Notes

*
*

## (Any other verb...)

### Requirements

*
*

### Steps

1.
1.

### Notes

*
*
  &lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;administration-manual-standards&quot;&gt;Administration Manual Standards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The administration manual will contain everything in the user manual as well as
information on how to use the system from a super user’s perspective. In most
cases this will cover configuration and user administration that other users do
not have access to. This may go into details on system installation, although
that particular could be a manual unto itself depending on the complexity of
the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;api--developer-manual-standards&quot;&gt;API / Developer Manual Standards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Description: There should always be a short statement describing the purpose
of the web service.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Request
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Authentication: If the web service requires a form of authentication
indicate that in the documentation so that consumers of the API know
that their program may need an account/key/credential to consume the
service.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Headers &amp;amp; Parameters: Document the required and optional HTTP headers
and parameters. Document whether the headers and parameters are in fact
optional or not.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Example Request: Include as many use cases as possible in example
requests. If the service is a POST, PUT, or a request with a message
associated, make sure to include an example of what that message looks
like.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Response
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Returned Attributes: Include all of the possible attributes one might
receive and their data type. Make sure to list whether the data is
always returned or is optionally returned.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Example Response: Include as many possible response cases as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a markdown template to be used when writing API documentation for RESTful
XML and JSON web services:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
  &lt;code&gt;
## Description



## Request

### Authentication

Authentication is not required for this service.

### Headers &amp;amp; Parameters

#### Headers

| Name                   | Format | Required? | Definition                                        |
| ---------------------- | ------ |:---------:| ------------------------------------------------- |
|                        |        | Y/N       |                                                   |

#### Parameters

| Name                   | Format | Required? | Definition                                        |
| ---------------------- | ------ |:---------:| ------------------------------------------------- |
|                        |        | Y/N       |                                                   |

### Example Request

**GET** URL


```json

```

```xml

```


## Response

### Returned Attributes

| Name                   | Format | Required? | Definition                                        |
| ---------------------- | ------ |:---------:| ------------------------------------------------- |
|                        |        | Y/N       |                                                   |

### Example Response

```json

```

```xml

```
  &lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;source-documentation-standards&quot;&gt;Source Documentation Standards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All methods and classes in our applications should be prefaced by RDoc
compatible documentation describing the intention of the class or method.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.ruby-lang.org/en/2.3.0/RDoc/Markup.html&quot;&gt;RDoc Markup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/08/15/project-documentation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/08/15/project-documentation.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Developer's Checklist</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This checklist guides developers through daily operations that will improve their personal efficiency and their communication with team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If it is the 1st or the 16th of the month, compile all time records on a per
client basis and send them in to your project management contact.
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Time records must conform to the following column set or minimally
contain the following information:
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Datetime Start&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Datetime End&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Duration - (Datetime Start - Datetime End) in hours to the second
decimal place&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Comment - Preferrably a URL linking to the issue, but a short
comment of a sentence or less will suffice when appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Task - The type of work being performed, conforming to the project
plan’s task types&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Project - The name of the project or product the time entry is
associated with&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Check any projects for open pull requests in need of review. Make sure when
reviewing pull requests:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Comment on specific lines if possible. Most pull requests should be
small enough to review line by line. Particularly if the submitting
developer has already left their own comments.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Make sure you’re comments convey an understanding of what’s going on in
the pull request. More than half of the reason for conducting code
review is increasing the knowledge and awareness of developers working
with the submitting developer.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Bad comments are short and vague (i.e. “Looks good :+1:”)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Good comments demonstrate understanding (i.e. “Replaced removing empty
characters with the gsub method with the more efficient tr method :+1:”)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Post your standup message to the #developers Slack channel. Answer these
three questions when applicable:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;What were you working on your last active day?&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;What were you planning on working on today?&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Are there any obstacles or issues that your teammates can help you with?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Before starting work on an issue, check and make sure that the specification
has enough detail.
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;We want to make sure we follow the DMAIC (Define, Measure, Analyze,
Implement, Control) cycle as closely as possible. Having enough
information is crucial to being able to properly follow the rest of the
steps in the process.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;It’s also helpful to have as many of the basic “5W1H” questions in the
answered in the specification.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who&lt;/strong&gt; does the specification concern? (usernames and roles are
helpful)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt; does the user need? (description of the feature or bug)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt; does the functionality need to be added or fixed? (URLs)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why&lt;/strong&gt; does this specification need to be addressed?&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt; does the issue occur or what times are important to the
specification (including deadlines)&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How&lt;/strong&gt; the stakeholders would like to see the issue resolved?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Specifications must also conform to our INVEST+E guidelines. Meaning
that issues must be:
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Independently addressable&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Negotiable&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Valuable&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Estimable&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Small&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Testable&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Examples included when possible&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Solve the problem selected
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Measure&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Analyze&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Implement&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Control… by implementing a pre-push hook on all of your projects. We have
continuous integration and deployment tools that monitor product quality.
However, having a basic pre-push hook will prevent you from submitting a
broken branch for approval.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;#!/bin/sh&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Brakeman&lt;/span&gt;
brakeman
&lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Rubocop&lt;/span&gt;
rubocop -c config/rubocop.yml
&lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Tests&lt;/span&gt;
rake &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;test&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When your work is ready for approval:
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Post any important metrics from the pre-push routine or relevant
benchmarks to explain your work&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Comment on the most important lines of your pull request&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Notify the correct @team on Github&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Post a link to the pull request in the Slack #developers channel&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When you finish an issue, go estimate more work in project backlogs.
Propose solutions and ask for more detail when necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plan what you can address in the next week as you proceed through the
current week. You want to make sure that when the weekly developer meeting
comes around that you have done all of the, “fishing” and that you don’t
have to obtain too many suggestions on what to work on next. You just need
to reconcile what priorities you can address with what the project manager
has obtained from the client, and proceed through the cycle again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/08/15/developers-checklist.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/08/15/developers-checklist.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Job Description: Junior to Mid-level Project Manager</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Project managers are responsible for gathering and organizing information on the scope, budget, and timeline of software development projects. As of July 24th, 2016 we have an opening for a junior to mid-level project manager in Philadelphia, PA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project managers are responsible for gathering and organizing information on the
scope, budget, and timeline of software development projects. Every week they
will be expected to run a meeting with the stakeholders of each project under
their care. During this meeting the work completed, underway, and work to be
performed during the next development sprint must be reviewed. Actual and
estimated length of time and cost for each work item must be communicated. At
the end of the meeting, any new specifications from the project stakeholders
must be gathered in accordance with our specification standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;primary-job-duties&quot;&gt;Primary Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Schedule and maintain regular scheduled meetings with stakeholders for
assigned projects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Review the work completed, underway, and upcoming on each assigned project
with the project’s stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Collect new specifications from project stakeholders according to INVEST+E
specification guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;File new specifications in each project’s Backlog milestone and communicate
the presence of new specifications for estimation to development staff.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compile and communicate the estimated timeline and cost for individual
tasks based on feedback from development staff.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Obtain sign off from project stakeholders for production deployments of
projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;secondary-job-duties&quot;&gt;Secondary Job Duties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assist with collection of development staff time records and invoicing at
the first and middle of the month.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assist with testing efforts prior to a project release.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assist with project documentation and training efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Assist with contract communications, including onboarding of clients and
subcontractors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills-and-qualifications&quot;&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verbal and Written Communication, Basic Accounting and Statistical Knowledge,
Spreadsheet and Word Processing Experience, Familiarity with Web Application and
Software Development&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;location-hours-and-terms&quot;&gt;Location, Hours, and Terms&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Center City Philadelphia, PA&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flexible hours with some neccessary meetings between 9am and 5pm Eastern&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Independent contractors, contract-to-hire is a possibility&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compensation is hourly and based on experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/07/24/junior-to-mid-level-project-manager-job-description.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/07/24/junior-to-mid-level-project-manager-job-description.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
